(Penny:)No. Yeah, I remember specifically.
(Penny:)You started by asking if I was from Mars
because my ass was out of this world.
(Howard:)Well, that does sound like me, but no.
SHELDON:
Is there some problem?
Yeah, um, listen,
I have to kind of sneak out for a while.
- All right. Goodbye.
- No, wait.
(Leonard:)If anyone asks you where I went,
you don't know.
- Where are you going?
- I can't tell you that.
Well, who would ask me?
(Leonard:)I can't tell you that either.
You brought me here to inform me
you can't tell me where you're going.
(Sheldon:)And you can't tell me who might ask?
(Leonard:)Yeah, I really didn't think this through.
- Leonard, a moment.
- What?
(Sheldon:)If someone...
And we don't know who this would be.
(Sheldon:)...does ask where you've gone,
what should I say?
(Howard:)I don't know.
Tell them I went to the office.
- Are you going to the office?
- No.
- Well, then how can I say it convincingly?
- Just say, "Leonard went to the office."